maxxis.com 2006-12-10

# Maxxis.com - Privacy Policy

## MAXXIS INTERNATIONAL PRIVACY POLICY

Maxxis International ("Maxxis") knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. The following policy address what information we collect from you and how we use that information. If you have additional questions that are not answered here, [click here](http://www.maxxis.com/contact_us/comments.asp) to contact us. 

**WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS**

This Privacy Policy covers Maxxis’s treatment of information, including personally identifiable information, that Maxxis gathers when you are accessing Maxxis’s Web site, purchasing Maxxis products (whether online or offline), or using Maxxis’s services (whether online or offline). Also, this Privacy Policy covers Maxxis’s treatment of any information, including personally identifiable information, that Maxxis’s business partners share with Maxxis. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Maxxis does not own or control, or to individuals that Maxxis does not employ or manage. 

**TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED AND WHAT IT IS USED FOR**

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our customers. 

_Personally Identifiable Information You Provide to Us_ : 

Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, Maxxis only collects personally identifiable information (information that identifies one individual from another) that you voluntarily provide to us. The types of personally identifiable information collected include: your first and last name; your physical address or postal address; your phone number; your credit card number; your credit card expiration date; your credit card security ID number; your email address; the date your account was opened; and details regarding your purchases. 

This information is used for purposes such as: creating your Maxxis account; billing your credit card when you make a purchase; crediting your credit card in the event that we issue you a refund; sending marketing communications and purchase confirmations to you (unless you have elected not to receive such information); sending surveys to you; responding to your requests for certain products and services; customizing the advertising and content you see; communicating with you about specials and new products; and improving the quality of your visit to the Maxxis Web site. 

You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. 

_Aggregate Data_ : 

We automatically collect and store the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet protocol address of the computer you are using, the browser software and the operating system you are using, the date and time you access our site, the areas of our site that you visit, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site. This data is anonymous in nature and does not contain any personally identifiable information. 

Maxxis only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use areas of the Web site or services, so that we can make the Web site appealing to as many customers as possible and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our site. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and our Web site, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. 

**HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED AND WHAT IT IS USED FOR**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Web site or services. Maxxis automatically receives and records information on our server logs about your visit using cookies, log analysis and other aggregate tracking technologies. 

_Cookies_ : 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Maxxis cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, and we do not combine the information collected through cookies with other information to tell us who you are. 

We may use cookies in order to enhance the user experience. Cookies help us to deliver information specific to your interests and to better analyze user traffic patterns so we can provide content that our visitors want. 

A Maxxis third-party advertiser cookie file may also be placed on your hard drive during your visit to our Web site. The purpose of these cookies is to help identify repeat visitors to our Web site. Cookies also may be used to collect aggregate statistics about your visit to our Web site. 

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. However, by refusing to accept a cookie, you may not be able to access some pages or features of our Web site. Also, Maxxis may not be able to provide you ith a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you. 

_Tracking Pixels_ : 

Emails that we send to you may contain a pixel image file to determine when and whether you have opened the email. Maxxis uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid s ending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, [click here](http://www.maxxis.com/contact_us/comments.asp) to contact us. 

_Third-Party Sources_ : 

For purposes such as improving personalization of our service, we may receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. 

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

Except as stated in this Privacy Policy, we neither share, rent nor sell your personally identifiable information with or to anyone. 

_Businesses That We Control_ : 

We may share your personally identifiable information with our parent company, subsidiaries or other affiliates that control, are controlled by, or under common control with Maxxis. 

_Businesses We Do Not Control_ : 

From time to time, we may be affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses may operate stores at Maxxis’s Web site or sell items to you through Maxxis’s Web site. In other situations, Maxxis may provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. We indicate when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share customer information that is related to the transaction with that affiliated business. 

We may send offers to certain customers on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, [click here](http://www.maxxis.com/contact_us/comments.asp) to contact us. 

_Agents_ : 

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and may need to share your personally identifiable information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include: fulfilling orders; delivering packages; sending postal mail; sending email; removing repetitive information from customer lists; analyzing data; providing marketing assistance; processing credit card payments; and providing customer service. Unless we tell you differently, we will not grant to Maxxis’s agents any right to use personally identifiable information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. 

_Disclosures Pursuant to Law_ : 

Certain federal, state, local, or other government regulations may require that we disclose personally identifiable information about you. In such cases, we will use reasonable efforts to disclose only the information required by law enforcement personnel. In addition, we may release personally identifiably information in order: to resolve customer or credit card company disputes; to exchange information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction; to bring action against someone who Maxxis reasonably believes may be violating the terms of this Privacy Policy or another agreement with Maxxis; or to bring action against someone who Maxxis reasonably believes may be causing injury to Maxxis, our employees, our Web site users, our customers, or others. 

**CONTROL OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION**

Our Web site allows you to choose not to provide personally identifiable information. However, if you opt not to disclose information to us, you may not be able to make a purchase or take advantage of certain features of Maxxis’s Web site. 

You may add or update certain personally identifiable information provided to us. However, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. 

You may request deletion of your Maxxis account by using our "contact us" form. However, some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account. 

You may choose to stop receiving email or other mail from us by clicking on the "to be excluded from this list and/or future mailing" link at the bottom of the Newsletter. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, the legal notices will still govern your use of the Maxxis Web site, and you are responsible for reviewing the legal notices for changes. 

**DISCLAIMER REGARDING OTHER SITES**

Our Web site may contain links to other sites. We have no control over the privacy practices of those other Web sites, and we recommend that you read the privacy policies of those other sites. 

**SAFEGUARDING OF INFORMATION**

We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the transmission of information that you submit to our Web site. This software encrypts the information that you input. In addition, Maxxis holds a Secure Server Certificate from VeriSign, a leading provider of Internet Trust Services. 

Your Maxxis account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to protect your account by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

While we use current industry standard procedures to protect your privacy, unfortunately, no data transmission or storage security can be guaranteed 100% of the time. In addition, third parties may unlawfully intercept or obtain information from our Web site. We do not promise that your personally identifiable information will remain private in such cases. 

**CHILDREN’S USE OF THE WEB SITE**

Maxxis recognizes the importance of children’s safety and privacy on the Internet. For this reason, and in compliance with certain laws, we do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children, nor do we offer any content targeted to children. We ask that children under the age of thirteen not use our site. 

**USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION AFTER A CHANGE OF BUSINESS**

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Maxxis, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Maxxis goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information may be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

**CERTAIN LEGALITIES**

By using the Maxxis Web site, you assent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any terms of this Privacy Policy, then please discontinue use of this Web site and do not provide us with any personally identifiable information. Maxxis reserves the ability to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. Continued use of the site by visitors signifies continued assent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as updated or amended at that time. Use of information we collect is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected. 

This Privacy Policy, and all of its graphics, logos, trademarks, and other intellectual property, is the property of Maxxis and is protected by copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. No reproduction of any intellectual property of Maxxis in this Web site or this Privacy Policy is allowed without the express written consent of Maxxis. 

**REVISIONS TO THE POLICY**

You can determine when the Privacy Policy was last updated by looking at the “last update” date at the bottom of this statement. If there are material and substantial changes to the Privacy Policy with regard to the manner in which Maxxis handles personally identifiable information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Web site. 

Policy last revised on 10/16/2006.
